Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 5. Constituent Services Files, 1976-2007 TJU.2010.01.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Local Services, 1976-2002; III.
  - Philadelphia port Senate hearings, 1990 (Box 1076, Folder 5)
  - Philadelphia ports, 1990 (Box 1076, Folder 6-7)
  - Pittsburgh Technology Council, 2000 (Box 1076, Folder 8)
  - Project funding, 1992-1994 (Box 1076, Folder 9)
  - Projects and issues, 1990-1993 (Box 1076, Folder 10-14)
  - Projects and issues, 1990-1993 (Box 1077, Folder 1-8)
  - Schuylkill Falls, 1986 (Box 1077, Folder 9)
  - State files, 1994-1995 (Box 1077, Folder 10-14)
  - State files, 1994-1995 (Box 1078, Folder 1-8)
  - State files, 1995-1997 (Box 1078, Folder 9-14)
  - State files, 1995-1997 (Box 1079, Folder 1)
  - State files, Allentown, 1990 (Box 1079, Folder 2)
  - State files, Erie, 1989-1991 (Box 1079, Folder 3)
  - State files, Lancaster, 1990-1992 (Box 1079, Folder 4)
  - State files, Philadelphia, 1991-1992 (Box 1079, Folder 5)
  - State files, Pittsburgh, 1990-1992 (Box 1079, Folder 6)
  - State files, Scranton, 1990-1992 (Box 1079, Folder 7)
  - State files, Wilkes-Barre, 1990 (Box 1079, Folder 8)
  - State requests, 2001 (Box 1079, Folder 9)
  - State requests, 2002 (Box 1079, Folder 10)